https://www.flpeacockbass.com/privacy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to footerPrivacy for FlPeacockBass.com Contact Us |Privacy PolicyBass On-Line (“BassOnLine.com, Hawghunter.net, iOutdoor.com, FlPeacockbass.com, BigoBass.com, Lakeokeechobeebassfishing.com, BassAuthority.com”) is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of the type of information we may gather about you, and how we may use or disclose that information. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Bass On-Line, which includes the guide services listed above, and not to other companies’ or organizations’ Web sites to which we link or which may link to us.Information About Visitors in GeneralIn general, our service automatically gathers information like the numbers of visitors, which we examine and use only in the aggregate. This helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can continue to improve our site. For example, FLPEACOCKBASS.COM uses a technology nicknamed “cookies” that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to enable us to identify you. Aside from information you may voluntarily provide to our partners and affiliates, we never provide information about you personally to third parties, though we may provide aggregate statistical information to our partners and affiliates so that they may improve the quality of their sites.Information About You in ParticularOccasionally, either we or a partner or affiliate will specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We will need certain information — such as name, Internet address, billing address, credit card number — in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. If we ever ask you for information about your interests, you may always decide whether or not to respond, and if ever you wish not to receive information about additional products or services, you may inform us and we will discontinue sending you such information.DisclosureWe do not disclose information about your individual visits or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies, other than as noted above.Privacy Policy ChangesIf we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always be fully informed of our privacy policy.If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, our practices, or your dealings with us, please click here.© 1998-2018,Bass On-Line | Privacy Policy | Terms and ConditionsBassOnline.com, Hawghunter.com, Hawghunter.net, FlPeacockbass.com, FlPeacockbass.net, BigOBass.com, LakeOkeechobeeBassFishing.com and BassAuthority.com are service marks of BassOnLine. All other trademarks are the property of their respective owners.To Contact Us at BassOnLine.com : Click Here.
